Personal Information:

Name: Mitra Mohammad Hosseini Sisakht

Birth Day: 1995-04-12

Country: Iran

Cell Phone: +98 9367482561

E-Mail: mhmitra.mh@gmail.com

I am an industrial Designer. I was born in Sisakht(Kohgiluye & Boyerahmad province), Grew up in Isfahan. I have always been interested in creating objects by hand when I was a child, but since I got familiar with different design fields, I knew industrial design and whatever related to it are in my interest zone. So overtime, this interest was transfered from creating things by hand in childhood to creating useful objects for life. As a result I took up Industrial Design as my major in the university.

After graduation from BCs program, I decided to work despite my desire to continue my studies in MCs peogram. After gaining valuable experiences during the years of working in multiple companies, now I intend to get to well established Politecnico di Milano University, to expand my knowledge in Design program.

Experiences:

2022	Working as Packaging Structure designer in Mirnegaar Graphic Printing and Packaging Company / (2022/04 - Now)
2021	Working as Packaging Structure designer in Teram Printing and Packaging Company / (2021/09/05 - 2020/12/ 21)
2020	Internship as graphic designer at Anil Pack packaging company / (2019/01/20 - 2020/11/20) / Isfahan - Iran
2018	Participation in the group exhibition of visual arts entitled Color Season / Photography Section / (2018/12/16 - 2018/12/20) / Tabriz - Iran
2015	Internship at Goharbafan (Auto Fabric & Seat Cover Manufacturer) / 120 hrs (University internship poject) / (2015/07 - 2015/09) / Isfahan - Iran
2015	Participated in the Isfahan city first fashion group show as fashion designer/ (2014/01) / Isfahan - Iran

Education:

2013 - 2018	Bachelor of Industrial Design / Tabriz Art University / Tariz - Iran GPA : 15.31(Out of 20)
2012	High school diploma in Mathematics & Physics / Banifateme High School / Tariz - Iran GPA: 13.36(Out of 20)

Achivements:

2022	A Design Award Competition / Winner of Iron A Design Award & Competition for One More
2020	Gensai Design & Planning Competition / GENSAI Design Award, with Life Saving Umbrela
2020	National Award of Packaging Design in Cultural Industries / Silver Award, with Jelveh

Operating Activities:

2018	Tarahi-Novin Student Quarterly Magazine Layout Design / Number 3 / Islamic Azad University,
	Science and Research Branch / Tehran - Iran
2018	Statue 3D Modeling for Dr. Mahmoud Golabchi International Architecture Festival / Pars
	University / Tehran - Iran

Certificates:

2020	Design: Creation of Artifacts in Society / online course by Coursera / (2020/08/15)
2020	Prototyping for Digital Products and Websites / online course by Gymnasium / (2020/08/03)
2020	UX Fundeamental Course / online course by Gymnasium / (2020/08/13)
2020	Fashion as Design Course / online course by Coursera / (2020/08/03)
2019	Fashion Design Course / 8 month / Danesh Ara Academy of Arts / (2014/01 - 2013/07) / Isfahan - Iran
2019	Product Design and Smart Home Workshop / Farshad Safari - Mohammad Hadi Heidari / Isfahan University of Art / (2018/12/22 - 2018/12/20) / Isfahan - Iran
2018	From Idea to Italy Workshop / 12 hrs / Nima Bavardi - Mohammad Afkhami / pin Design Studio / (2018/05/01 - 2018/04/25) / Tehran - Iran
2018	The Introduction of Technology in Fashion, Design And Garment / 12 hrs / Noushin Moghtader - Serjo Milani - Enriqo Rosso / East Azarbaijan Industrial Management Organazation / (2017/11/15 - 2017/11/12) / Tabriz - Iran
2018	Entrepreneurship workshop titled "Entrepreneurship in Art" and "Trade and Sales Skills of Artistic Products" / 4 hrs / Tabriz Islamic Art University / (2018/03/11) / Tariz - Iran
2018	Gensai Design Workshop / Professor Jero Sagara - Rosita Farnam / Embassy of Japan in Tehran / (2018/02/25) / Tehran - Iran
2016	Car Modeling with Clay Workshop / 8 hrs / Behrooz Mahmoudzade / Tabriz Islamic Art University / (2016/02/25) / Tariz - Iran

Languages:

Lorish: Mother tongue English: Intermediate Korean: Beginner

Persian : Native Beginner : Beginner

Software Skills:

